(Amy:)I'm so glad you like it.
(Sheldon:)I'm prepared to say I love it,
(Sheldon:)as soon as I confirm there
are no hobos aboard.
(Sheldon:)OK.
(Leonard(on phone):)Raj, I got it.
(Leonard(on phone):)Bye.
(Leonard(on phone):)That was your daddy.
(Leonard(on phone):)He wanted me to say that he misses--
Why am I doing this?
Happy Valentine's Day!
(Leonard:)Flowers and chocolates?
(Leonard:)Somebody's trying
to get me out of my panties.
(Penny:)Don't be surprised if you
find five chocolates missing
(Penny:)and three gross coconut
ones with a bite taken out.
(Penny:)It came that way when I bought it.
(Leonard:)Got you a little something, too.
Oh, jewelry!
Oh, my God. Lakers tickets?!
(Leonard:)It gets better. Instead of me,
you can take someone
(Leonard:)-who will actually enjoy it.
-Ohh!
(Penny:)You are the best boyfriend ever.